<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Most of the clothing stores in the shopping arcade are small, one-story affairs, with a limited selection of goods on offer.
		 The establishment before you appears to be the exception to this rule, and takes the form of a huge, two-story clothing department bearing the sign 'Nyan's Clothing Emporium'.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_GREETING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping through the open pair of wide, glass doors, you find yourself in a large, modern-looking clothing store.
		 As you walk through the building, you discover that not only is this the largest shop in the arcade, but that it's also the busiest.
		 Crowds of shoppers block many of the aisles that you'd like to walk down, and every member of staff that you see is busily occupied with other customers.
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding that it might be best to try and find a smaller, quieter clothing store, you turn around and start to head for the exit.
		 As you do so, you hear a nervous voice calling out from behind you,
		 [nyan.speech(E-Erm, excuse me? C-Can I help you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning once more, this time in the direction that the timid voice came from, you find yourself face-to-face with a lesser cat-girl.
		 As you look into her bright blue eyes, her cheeks instantly turn a deep shade of red, and she glances down at the floor and starts shuffling her feet. 
		[nyan.speech(H-Hello... T-There's nobody else available, you see, s-so I thought maybe I could help. Oh, erm, I-I'm Nyan... I probably should have said that first... W-Welcome to my store...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		If it wasn't for the fact that she's wearing a staff uniform, and has a little name tag pinned to her blouse reading 'Nyan; Store Manager', you're not sure if you would have believed that she's the store's owner.
		 In an attempt to put the anxious cat-girl at ease, you ignore the fact that she's visibly trembling and explain your situation to her,
		 [pc.speech(Pleased to meet you, Nyan, it's an impressive place you've got here! I was having a little difficulty finding anything in amongst all these crowds, however...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(O-Oh, sorry! E-Everything we have on display can also b-be found back in our stockroom. F-Follow me and I'll show you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		In what appears to be an almost desperate attempt to escape further conversation, Nyan hurries past you and rushes off towards a door bearing the sign 'Staff Only'.
		 Doing as she instructed, you follow her through the door into the store's stockroom.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_GREETING_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping through the open pair of wide, glass doors, you find 'Nyan's Clothing Emporium' to be just as busy as ever.
		 Crowds of shoppers block almost every aisle, and if it wasn't for Nyan's offer to personally show you around her stockroom, you don't think you'd ever manage to get any shopping done in here.
	</p>
	<p>
		Scanning around for any sign of the store's nervous owner, you suddenly hear a familiar squeak coming from behind you,
		 [nyan.speech(A-Ah! H-Hello again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You turn around to see Nyan looking down at her feet as she shuffles them about on the shop's laminate flooring.
		 [pc.speech(Hi, Nyan, how are y-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(I-I'm fine! T-Thanks for asking,)] Nyan bursts out, interrupting you in her haste to answer.
		 [nyan.speech(I-I can show you the stockroom again if y-you'd like! F-Follow me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following Nyan into her store's stockroom once again, you wonder what to take a look at this time...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_GREETING_REPEAT_PREGNANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Entering the store, you're surprised to find that Nyan is nowhere in sight.
		 Pushing through the throngs of people, you manage to catch one of the employees not busy with a customer, and upon asking after Nyan, you're pointed in the direction of the stock room.
	</p>
	<p>
		Entering the familiar room, you discover that Nyan is indeed in here, murmuring to herself behind a stack of boxed clothing.
		 Wringing her hands and staring at her feet, something has quite clearly got her more worked up than usual, and you notice that she jumps a little as she sees you approach.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(What's wrong, Nyan?)]
		 you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(O-Oh... well um...)] she says haltingly. [nyan.speech(Do y-you remember when w-we...you know...)] She blushes fiercely and says in a very quiet voice, [nyan.speech(Had s-sex...?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You smile at the memory and nod.
		 Nyan smiles nervously back, before continuing,
		 [nyan.speech(W-Well my tummy felt a little funny a-after so I took a t-test and...a-and...)]
		 She closes her eyes and takes a deep breath, bunching up the bottom of her skirt as if gathering her courage before blurting out,
		 [nyan.speech(I'm pregnant with your baby!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After her outburst, she just stands there; eyes scrunched closed, trembling hands clenching her skirt, she seems to be waiting for an admonishment.
		 Stepping forwards, you sweep her into your arms, wishing that you'd been able to record the surprised squeak that bursts out of her mouth.
		 She blinks in surprise as you hold her close, before pulling back a little and staring at you with open-mouthed shock.
		 [nyan.speech(W-W-What? You're not a-angry?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You hold her at arm's length for a moment, smiling as you shake your head.
		 [pc.speech(Why would I be angry? This is great news!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		A visible tension seems to melt from her entire being as the nervous cat-girl cutely smiles back and snuggles into your [pc.arms].
		 [nyan.speech(W-Will you come b-by and visit from time to t-time?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You instantly agree, and can't help but grin as you notice that she's looking happier than you've ever seen her before.
		 Still nestled against your chest, Nyan mumbles,
		 [nyan.speech(D-Did you need something w-while we're in the s-stockroom?)]
	</p>
	<p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_STOCK_ROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The stockroom of Nyan's Clothing Emporium looks pretty much exactly as you'd expected it be.
		 Ceiling-height shelving units are stocked full of clothes, shoes, and accessories of all different sorts, and there's a distinctive 'new clothing' smell lingering in the air.
	</p>
	<p>
		Nyan's heels clatter across the laminate flooring as she hurries to retrieve a notepad that she uses to track what's currently in stock.
		 Rushing back over to you, she fumbles with the little pad and almost drops it on the floor.
		 [nyan.speech(A-Ah! S-Sorry, I don't usually interact with customers, s-so sorry if I'm a little unprofessional... A-Anyway, let me know what you'd like t-to see, and I'll show y-you what I've got in stock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You start to thank the nervous cat-girl, but she suddenly squeaks out and cuts you off,
		 [nyan.speech(O-Oh! A-and I forgot! I-I was going to do a t-trial of offering to buy old clothes from customers, s-so if you wanted to, I-I could buy some old clothing from you...
			 O-Oh, I interrupted you... S-Sorry...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thanking Nyan for her time, you explain to her that you need to get going now.
		 Hurrying to put her little notepad away, she stutters,
		 [nyan.speech(W-well, thanks for choosing to s-shop here! If you ever want t-to come back, just find me and I-I'll show you what's in stock back here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can respond, Nyan turns around and runs off deeper into the stockroom.
		 You're pretty sure that there aren't any other exits in that direction, and that she was just unable to continue the conversation any longer.
	</p>
	<p>
		You step out of the stockroom, and, after pushing your way through a crowd of customers that's loitering around the store's exit, you head back out into the shopping arcade.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_EXIT_EMBARRASSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having been deserted by the panic-stricken cat-girl, you walk out of the stockroom and head towards the shop's exit.
		 After pushing your way through a crowd of customers who're loitering around the large glass doors, you head back out into the shopping arcade.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
